So, first I want to know what is a processing fee.
What is it?
I don't know.
Yes. But I want to know one sentence.
This is a fixed fee or a variable fee taken by the bank for each successful loan disbursement.
There is no success.
It is non-refundable.
Okay. For each successful application.
Not only successful.
There is only one application.
There is only one successful application.
Okay.
There is a function letter.
If you want to work with it, you have to pay the full fee.
Yes.
Actually,
I want to know what is this processing fee.
Because first of all,
I also want to know.
Is there a way
to avoid this fee?
So, you have to write, this is a mandatory fee.
Next, you have to write,
private banks minimum fee,
public banks minimum fee,
public banks variable fee.
There is a guide.
There is no guide.
You have to write, yes.
Because first of all, I want to know,
how to avoid this.
I don't want to know.
Property check charge. I know how much.
I have checked the property.
Legal and technical.
My brother is my lawyer.
That's why I have written.
Legal and technical means,
legal and technical.
Title search report.
Title is clear.
This is mandatory.
The bank does it.
Even if you have done it,
the report will not be accepted by the bank.
The customer has to
be fully proofed.
You have to save money.
The first thing you have to do is
save money.
Don't worry,
we have the same page.
We have the same page.
This is one of the cheapest
fees.
Google flight service.
What is the name of this app?
Search and check.
I have to sit in a chair.
I haven't done anything.
You have to give a comfortable table.
If you are a broker,
I can do a broker.
Intelligence has become cheap.
It has become so cheap.
Processing fee.
Variable fee.
Maximum apply.
10,000 cash.
You have to pay 10,000 cash.
You have to pay
at least
10,000 cash.
You have to pay 10,000 cash.
If I feel like
how to save this money,
I already know how to do it.
I have to pay
2,000 cash.
I have written 2,000 cash.
Now I have to enter the reality
and accept the actual money.
I have to pay 10,000 cash.
And you have to write
that these banks are
one of the highest
who charge processing fees.
Highest?
What do you do after so many years?
What do I do?
I have to give
a risk model.
I have to pay high risk
and high interest.
I have to pay maximum
because there are more chances of default.
What do you do after so many years?
I have to pay
maximum interest.
I have to buy
furniture from No EMI.
I have to pay
maximum interest.
What is this?
This bank will also give you an idea.
What is this? 3 million?
You can put it on the website.
Again, this is
one of the highest.
This bank is known
for the highest amount of processing fees
in the whole market.
Property check charges
and technical
guidance search
This bar
1, 2, 3,
put one at a time.
And this bar is small.
This is the width of the bar.
If it is the width, 1, 2, 3, 4,
it will split.
Why put one at a time?
Then you can solve the problem.
You have to keep the standard
on the side of the panel.
No.
If 1, 2, 3, 4
came down, how easy would it be
2 is here,
and you have to put a line
like this.
Then you don't have to do
this independently.
And the same thing happens here too.
I used to think that
1, 2, 3, 4, who can do this?
Then you open a small bar
and give all the sequentialities.
And it will sit.
How many blocks is this?
It is an external thing.
It is a repeatable thing.
Yes.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
it will come down one by one.
And if the width is less, it is okay.
If the mat is normal from the top,
if it comes like this,
then it will come down.
It will flow.